and right now you're wondering why were kurda and asari mad at you i want you to find the answer
to that question figuring it out is your next assignment that feels so much better
what the hell man get up you're planning on just lying here all day it's monday and we only get one
full day off all week you should take advantage of your free time while you can i'm fine not like
there's any place i'm dying to go
Well, I hope you're at least planning to get some proper rest over spring break.
You know, if you're not planning to be going home.
I'm just excited to finally be getting some laundry done, man.
I feel bad having the dorm staff do it for me, so it piles up.
I can't wait to get home and take advantage of my youth team status with all the ladies.
Sounds fun.
It's easy for us to visit our families, but I know it's harder for you.
I'm sorry.
It sucks to be you!
It's cool. I'm fine.
It'll be a good opportunity to find out more about everyone.
I can sneak into your rooms and check out all your nudie mags.
Don't you dare!
Well, boys, I'm off to Shonen and Kanagawa.
Most of my friends from home are getting together there.
Oh, yeah? That's cool.
Gotta be other guys from outside Tokyo who are here over break, right?
That second-year Akutsu's family is somewhere outside the Kanto area.
Maybe you could hang with him.
Hell no!
Don't even go there!
I have so much I still have to pack up when I go home.
Yeah, me too.
Mm-hmm.
Now that I think about it,
I don't know much about the promoted players.
I haven't really talked to any of them since the intra-squad game.
But the type of pass should have clued you in.
Owie!
Pay attention to our movements!
Is that why?
Because I still haven't mastered all these skills that come naturally to them.
I don't think they really see me as part of the team yet.
And it sucks.
Maybe I should give my friends back home a call.
I can't.
What would I even tell them?
It's been almost a whole month.
I haven't done anything yet.
There's nothing to tell them.
Shut up, wiener!
Sitting around's no help!
I'm gonna spend the whole day in training!
Again!
I don't care if it's our day off.
I'll work hard and get better in all of them!
Ashito?
Oh, good!
You're still here!
Wanna come check out the high school?
You haven't been to see it yet, have you?
You're going to the same school as me,
so I can show you around in advance?
Come on!
What the heck are you thinking, Hana?
For real?
First of all, this is a boys' dorm.
You can't just barge in here like you own the place.
Well, you don't have a cell phone,
so how else am I supposed to contact you?
I don't care about the stupid school.
Let's go.
I can't.
I have stuff to do.
Yeah, right.
Oh, crap.
I can't believe I forgot to put on cologne before I left.
How am I going to bless the hotties?
You're on the youth team.
I figured you'd be stronger than this.
Come on, put your back into it.
What?
You were bored, right?
I rescued you, huh?
Wasn't this a good call?
Aren't you so glad I thought of it?
At least say something!
Are you trying to injure me here?
Uh, what?
That reminds me.
I should probably give you this before I forget.
Here you go.
Um, I have no idea what this is.
You better.
It's your meal plan.
What?
Another one?
Hey, listen up.
If you want a strong body that isn't injury prone,
you need to eat better.
You made me one before.
You don't have to keep on doing it, though.
I'll eat whatever I want when I'm hungry.
These are good for the next six months.
So whenever you're ready,
feel free to say thanks, Hana, so much.
Interesting.
Every time I see this girl,
the same thought goes through my head.
I can't help asking myself,
where did this weirdo come from?
You little sneak, Ashito.
What the heck is going on here?
When did you become so close to that tasty snack,
and what the hell is she thinking?
How long are you going to be around?
Why don't you come hang out with the two of us instead?
I'm back.
You're pretty popular.
Hold on.
Where's yours?
Not hungry?
I'm just not really into desserts and stuff.
It's cool.
Good for you!
Proper nutrition is important
for growing professional athletes.
Here's a fun factoid for you.
When Zico came to Japan,
he would always yell at players
and call them unprofessional
whenever they would forge themselves on junk.
So what's the deal with you?
You want to be a nutritionist or something?
Or something.
I want to be a doctor of sports medicine.
That's why I have so many supplemental classes
on my schedule every day.
Keeps me busy, but it's cool.
I'm a real hard worker.
Sounds like it.
Why were Kurata and Asari mad at you?
I want you to find the answer to that question.
You could at least pretend to be impressed.
No, I am.
I'm sorry.
It's not you.
This sucks.
I can't focus on anything other than playing.
I should be training right now.
If I work at it,
I know I can get better
and prove to them that I belong.
I have to.
All right, here we are.
Welcome to Tokyo Myosin High.
So Tokyo Asperion is affiliated with this school,
which means that anybody playing on the youth team
who wants to go here can enroll on a scholarship.
Pretty cool, huh?
It makes the tuition super cheap,
and it's easier to focus on soccer.
All of the events and classes are scheduled
around your training time.
I know.
It's because of the scholarship
that my mom doesn't have to go bankrupt because of me.
Well, I mean,
you did move here from Ehime after all,
so it's got to be a way bigger deal for you.
I need to get back to my training.
Huh?
Glad I know how to get to school now.
Thanks, Hana.
Later.
Wait!
Rest days are important.
Take them.
Huh?
You're training so much,
but are you making all of those hours count?
Charging in blindly doesn't achieve anything.
Since I met you,
I always admired the intense fire I saw in your eyes.
But then there were other times,
it was different.
Those fiery eyes looked more angry and on edge.
Yeah?
Where's this coming from?
Because you barely even know me.
I know what I saw at the tryouts
and in the intra-squad game.
That dangerous look you get?
Like you're about to self-destruct or something.
It makes me worry.
I'll tell you why.
He was like that, too.
My favorite player that you remind me of, I mean.
Okay, look.
You keep bringing up this favorite player of yours,
but what am I supposed to do exactly?
I don't get it!
Nope, you sure don't.
And another thing.
Quit doing this kind of stuff.
A pretty girl paying special attention to me?
People are gonna get the wrong idea.
I've had this body my whole life.
I know its needs.
You don't have to worry, okay?
I'll be just fine.
Look, I'm never gonna be this dude
because I'm me, Ashito Aoi, genius forward.
You're trying to turn me into someone else.
Stop it!
I'm not whoever this guy is, okay?
Be delusional all you want,
but leave me out of it!
That's never what I was trying to do at all.
All I wanted to do today was practice!
If there's something I can't do,
I have to master it as soon as I can.
I've been watching the rest of the team play.
I know how far behind I am.
I've only got three years on this team.
I'm on a time crunch here.
I've been telling you I want to practice,
so just let me do it!
I appreciate you looking out for me,
but you don't know what it's like to be on this side,
so you really shouldn't be messing with...
Huh?
Hey, what about your bike?
I knew it, man.
I knew there was no way any girl would be hanging out with you
because she actually liked you.
Wait, what?
You know something?
You're kind of clueless when it comes to being aware
of how other people feel.
I noticed it yesterday while I was watching you in the game.
Huh?
Starting today, I hope you will dedicate yourselves to your studies
and perfecting your skills as soon as you...
Henri?
No way.
I never thought I'd run into you at this school.
You seem too smart to go to a place like this.
Yes, well, if I want to end up in my chosen profession,
I figured it would be best for me to attend the same school
that the players do.
You really are quite the strange one, aren't you?
Whoa, Yuma, wait a second.
What's the deal?
Hey, man, the deal?
What do you mean?
Um, isn't that the daughter of Asperion's sponsor?
Do you really know her well enough to joke with her?
Dude, my mom's been a house cleaner for her family for ages.
I know her just fine.
She and I go way back to when we were snot-nosed kids.
So, you check out the class yet?
A pretty interesting lineup we've got here, don't you think?
There's me, you, Takeshima, Asari, Kuroda, Togashi, and...
I noticed it yesterday while I was watching you in the game.
Um, I don't get it.
What do you mean, Otomo, huh?
No, I'll...
I'll just think it over.
Peek-a-boo, Ashito, Aoi.
It's been ten days.
Have you found your answer?
Ashito, I heard you made Hana cry the other day.
Man, too quick to make a move.
And even quicker to get dumped.
If you were wondering, Hana Ichijo is not in our class.
Sorry if that crushes your dreams.
According to my investigative notes on cute girls here,
she's in Advanced English.
And it's in a different building,
so you probably won't see her around much.
You know, when you make girls cry, you've got 24 hours.
To apologize, that is.
That's what all my research says, anyway.
It's been ten days now, hasn't it?
I guess the love story's over.
You're obviously struggling with something over here.
Just don't drag it out till the start of the league.
I mean, the B team plays competitive matches, too, you know?
That's what's great about the youth team.
It's a small enough number that we get more chances to play than usual.
The B team actually plays in a league, too,
so you can rack up some game time along with the rest of us.
So then, we compete, too?
Right.
I don't get it.
I'm saying that I get that I don't get it now.
Okay, whatever.
I don't want to talk to you.
Leave us alone.
I'm an idiot.
You know that.
I have no idea what you're thinking unless you tell me.
But still, that kind of came out of nowhere.
Sure, it was totally my bad.
But did you have to cry?
What?
Also, I don't understand why all of us can't just get along.
And there's not much I can do about something I don't get.
So let's talk it through.
First, the 11 on 21.
You want to know what I was thinking during that play?
I'll tell you what was going through my head.
I wanted to hold it up at the front of the goal
and then pass it out to the wing.
Then turn and run.
That's when I'd get him behind Akutsu,
pick up the return pass,
and shoot and score from there.
So there you go.
That's what I was thinking at the time.
But I was up against Akutsu.
So from your perspective,
you didn't think I could handle it.
You thought I couldn't get past him.
That it?
You got upset with me because I was too reckless?
I've had 10 days to think about this.
And it's the scenario that makes the most sense.
I have no idea if I'm right.
But I do know this.
I want to get out on the field together
and score some goals.
Don't you?
All I've been thinking about
is how to make that happen.
Anyway, that's all I've got.
I've said my piece.
Now you.
Like you said before,
it might take a while
for this year's first years to get along.
We've got quite a few characters this time, don't we?
The promoted players are conscientious,
while Aoi and the others are more relaxed.
They're not on the same page at all.
Especially Aoi.
Are you sure this is the right way to do it?
Fukuda,
your coaching methods have worked so well up to now.
Maybe if our advice was more direct...
Bad idea.
Nozomi,
that only make you feel better.
Giving players all the answers right away.
That's just the lazy approach.
They have to use their brains.
That's the point.
Aoi's case is particularly delicate.
I just hope things work out
the way you say they will.
He's on the B-team, Nozomi.
So it's on you for now.
Everybody knows that a coach
can make or break their players.
Ashito, well,
he'll figure out the answer.
Even if he does take the long way around to do it.
That sounds great.
You want to have a soccer discussion?
I'm interested.
Thanks, Aoi.
What the hell, man?
So, we're talking about
the 11-on-21 game we had last week, huh?
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
I didn't expect him to be so open to talking about it.
In that case,
looks like it's still your turn.
Huh?
I'm curious.
You must have had ideas
on how to score in that moment
that didn't involve taking on Akutsu,
right?
Yeah, duh.
They want to know.
I can talk to them about it.
Okay, check this out.
My first idea involved a crosser.
I would have passed to Tachibana
on the left here.
Then he would have sent it
to the opposite wing.
That's when I would have made a run
into the middle.
Overlapping on the right,
Asuri would have sent in the cross.
And then,
I would have scored.
I'm following.
There was some space
on the right at the time,
you see.
It's so cool
that I can talk about soccer like this,
even if I'm not on the field.
My second thought
was to offload it.
Like to Roland or Tachibana
in front of the goal.
Then a bunch of us
could have run towards the keeper.
That would confuse the crap
out of the opposition.
Since I was closest to the goal,
someone could have hit a long pass to me,
and I would have scored.
In the end,
they're just like me.
They all love soccer.
Maybe now we can understand each other.
My third idea
was a bit more unlikely.
But before Akutsu
had time to get to me,
I could have fainted
and passed to Tachibana.
But then aimed at the goal
instead and scored, huh?
That's enough.
Just stop.
Why do all these brilliant ideas
end with you scoring, huh?
Tell you what.
Stop obsessing over scoring the goals,
then maybe we can talk.
I agree on that point.
It sure would make a huge difference
if you were asking me
to thrive on the youth team.
Hold on a second.
Is that it?
Is that the reason
you two got mad at me?
Are you kidding me?
I'm a Ford, you guys.
Why wouldn't I be thinking
about scoring?
Stop obsessing over scoring goals.
The moment a forward
starts thinking like that,
he's done.
The whole point of coming to Asperion
was to become
the best forward in the world.
Well then, good for you.
I still don't even know
how you made it on the youth team.
It really pisses me off
thinking about my junior teammates
who didn't make it
because you stole their spot.
What are you talking about?
Stole it?
Otomo,
this has nothing to do with you.
Ashito and I fought
alongside each other
at the tryouts
with our careers on the line.
We fought hard.
Failure wasn't an option
and we had to go through hell.
If you've got a problem with that,
I won't stay quiet.
As for taking a spot
away from your teammates,
that's a bunch of crap
and you know it.
Get over yourself, Asari.
We earned our spots
and you know it.
Takashima,
Kurada,
let go!
Asari,
what Otomo's saying is true.
You went too far.
You can't say that.
I can't believe it.
They were pissed off at me
because I was focused
on being a Ford
and making goals.
That's just ridiculous.
No way.
That can't be all of it.
It just doesn't feel right.
There must be more
to what they said.
Coach Nozomi!
There you are, Ali.
Good.
I actually wanted to talk to you
because next week,
you'll be a starter.
However,
I need to see you make a play
that proves you completed
the assignment I set you.
If you can't do that,
I won't field you in a match
for the next three months.
So act as if your life
depends on it.
Next time on Aorashi, Tokyo Metropolis League Match 1, Seikyo High School.